tired?
疲れた?
I'm just a little tired.
ちょっとだけ疲れました
Are you a little tired?
ちょっと疲れた?
There's no break.
休憩はないよ
It's a shame that there are no breaks.
休憩ないのやばいですね
Because I moved from here to here.
こっちからの、こっちに移動したから
It was an anniversary.
記念日だった
記念日だったですよ
There's a lot of sperm here, a lot of it.
こっちいっぱい精子、いっぱいあるからさ
Look at that amount of tissues.
見て、あのティッシュの量
That's terrible.
やばいね
But, you're still doing well.
だけどさ、まだ元気なんだよね
Why?
なんでなんでしょ
After all, as I said earlier,
やっぱり、さっきも言ったけどさ、
I can't contain my excitement anymore, can I?
もう興奮が収まらないんじゃないの?
I want to see the real thing in front of my eyes.
本物を目の前にしてみたいな
Moreover, the moment I stopped the camera, something happened today.
しかもさ、カメラ止めた瞬間さ、なんか今日、
The camera stopped for a moment.
今カメラ一瞬止めたじゃん
Please stop. At that time, I actually thought...
止めてさ、その時に、実はちょっと、
Um, what?
あの、何?
Erokos?
エロコス?
I brought it with me, so I'd like you to come over for a while.
持ってきたんで、ちょっと来させたいんですけど、
That's what I was told.
みたいな感じで言われちゃって
I've actually done it.
実際にしてきたね
That's right.
そうなんだよね
Since you said that, will you let me come?
って言われちゃったから、来させちゃう?
Something like that?
みたいな感じのノリ?
By the way, what I have prepared is...
ちなみにだけどさ、用意してるのがさ、
There's only one kind, do you have it ready?
ちょっと一種類しかなくて、用意してるんですか、
That's what I brought.
その持ってきてもらったのが
It's black and white, which do you prefer?
白と黒だけどさ、どっちが好き?
I like white.
白が好き
Right?
でしょ?
It's white, right?
白でしょ?
It's white.
白です
Apparently, they said that white would definitely suit her.
白が絶対に似合うだろうなって言われらしいよ
TRUE?
本当?
Well, it seems like the fans know that.
やっぱね、ファンには分かってるらしい
As expected.
さすがです
I'll try changing it again.
それ一回着替えてみるよ
Let's change.
着替えましょう
I think I'll try changing my clothes and take some clothes with me.
着替えてみて、着替えしもちょっと取っていこうかな
Can I change my clothes?
着替えしも?
Even changing clothes.
着替えしも
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけね
ちょっとだけ
I guess I'll take just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ取っていこうかな
good?
いい?
Elcos.
エルコス
This is Elcos.
これでエルコス
This is black.
これ黒じゃん
What's inside?
中身は?
The inside is white.
中身は白
Just have it once.
ちょっと一回持ってて
I've been getting into it lately.
最近ハマってるんですよね
Well, maybe a little more.
いやー、もうちょっとかな
Was it good?
よかったですか?
Elkos is.
エルコスは
It's filled with paint.
いっぱいで塗るんですね
Looks like I'll have a good look at it.
ちゃんと見しようらしい
Well, I don't like that, you know.
まあ、嫌だよね、それはね
I don't like it because it's already used.
使用済みだから嫌だよね
Used.
使用済み
That's a bit of a problem.
ちょっと困りますね
picture?
え?
Like.
みたいな
Something like that.
なんか さ
Tintin.
タンタン
What is it?
何なの?
pants?
パンツ?
The number of reporters on WoW is decreasing.
すごいの記者数を落としてますよね
Just for the heck of it, I don't let anyone do cosplay.
ここぞとばかりにさ、コスプレなんかさせてなくて、
It seems like he wants to bully me.
いじめたいらしい
It seems like you want to delete it.
消去したいらしい
There are a lot of them though.
いっぱいあるけど
Well, just come on.
まあ、なんかちょっと、来てよ
As you like.
好きなように
As you like?
好きなように?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
Sorry for a moment.
ちょっとごめん
I don't know.
俺わかんない
Don't you know?
わかんない?
I see.
なるほど
Well then, let's go.
じゃあ、いきます
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Do you see this?
これ見る?
yes.
はい
Is this an arm?
これ腕か
This is your arm.
これが腕で
This is it?
これが?
Is this below?
これが下に?
perhaps.
多分
Shall we take this one time?
一回これ取ろうか
Shall we take this?
これ取ろうか
I agree.
そうだね
I'll change my clothes.
着替えちゃいます
Let me take out just how many.
何個だけ出させて
What's just there?
何そこだけ?
I don't know.
わかんない
I can't get the button off.
ボタン取れないよ
Turn up your skirt a little.
ちょっとスカートめくっとして
Service time?
サービスタイム?
Are you getting changed?
着替えられてる?
Do you want to change?
着替えますか?
Are you getting changed?
着替えられてる?
Do you understand properly?
ちゃんとわかる?
How high can I raise this?
これさ、どこまで上げるの?
What kind of cosplay did you bring?
どういうコスプレを持ってきたの?
Don't you have any sense?
センスない?
What kind of cosplay?
どういうコスプレ?
You brought it.
持ってきたんだね
What's the sense?
センス何?
That's it.
あれでしょ
I don't think her breasts are that big.
そんなに胸ないなとか思うけど
No breasts?
胸ない?
I don't have that kind of chest.
そんな胸ないな
There is, but I feel like it's probably missing something.
あるけど、多分なんか足りない気がする
I don't want to show it too much.
あんまり映したくないね
This is it, this time.
これ さ、今回ってんじゃん
I want to show you the finished product.
出来上がった状態を見せたいよね
I see.
なるほどね
Zirashi Paver.
ジラシプレーバー
Looks scary.
怖いそう
Hurry, hurry.
早く早く
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ちなさい
Just a moment, just a glimpse.
ちょっとじゃあ、チラッと
A glimpse.
チラッと
Seriously, what is this?
マジでさ、これ何?
What kind of cosplay?
どういうコスプレ?
Does it match?
合ってる?
It fits.
合ってるよ
The socks are also white.
靴下も白に
which one?
どれ?
That's true, like this time.
それがあるやろ、今回みたいな
The one with no socks.
靴下これないやつだ
there is.
あります
Here it is.
こちらです
It comes off with your nails.
爪で取れてる
white?
白い?
It's a little erotic.
ちょっとエロいな
surely.
確かに
Seriously, what kind of cosplay?
マジでどういうコスプレ?
There is.
あるよ
あるんだ
Is it visible?
映ってる?
Properly?
ちゃんと?
It's showing properly.
ちゃんと映ってる
But it looks surprisingly good.
でも意外とちゃんと映ってる
I'm lucky to be able to see this live,
これね、幸せなことに、生でこうやって見れてるのさ、
Because it's just me.
俺だけだからさ
To the actors and the people who prepared it,
男優さんたちにも、用意した人たちにも、
I'll hide it so you can see how it's finished.
ちょっと出来上がった姿を見てくれて隠れてるから
I was watching you change your clothes.
生着替え見てんだ
Yeah.
うん
That's cheating.
ズルいね
That's cheating, isn't it?
ズルいでしょ
I feel like this is just my privilege.
ここはちょっと、俺だけの特権っていうかさ
Did it break?
切れたの?
Yeah.
うん
It broke.
切れた
Has it broken?
切れた?
I think so.
と思う
It fits.
合ってる
Well then.
じゃじゃーん
Does this match?
合ってるこれ?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It really suits you.
やっぱ似合うね
It's cute.
可愛いね
Does it match?
合ってる?
A little naughty.
ちょっとエッチ
It fits.
合ってる
Yeah, that's about it.
うん、このくらいです
It fits.
合ってる
It suits you.
合ってるよね
It's right, it's right.
合ってる合ってる
It suits you.
合ってるよね
Well, it kinda fits.
まぁちょっと、合ってるわ
It suits you.
合ってるよね
It fits.
合ってる
It suits you.
似合うじゃん
Is it okay to cosplay?
コスプレやっていいの?
this.
これ
Do you do cosplay?
コスプレとかすんの?
You said you didn't have a boyfriend.
彼氏いないって言ったもんね
If I had a boyfriend, I'd like to work as a maid.
彼氏いたらメイドさんとかしてみたいけどね
Well, I'll get that one some time.
じゃあそれもちょっと今度もらうわ
I'll have it all done this way.
全部こうしてもらうわっていう
I'll take some of that.
ちょっともらうわ、それ
Maid, please remember this.
メイドさんね、覚えておく
When a lot of people say they want to come as a maid,
メイド来たいっていう声が溢れたら、
Want to see a maid?
メイド見たい?
If it overflows, I'll wear maid's clothes and no bra or pandas.
溢れたら、メイドの服にノーブラノーパンダね
That's a naughty cosplay.
エッチなコスプレですね
How about playing outdoors without wearing a bra or panda?
ノーブラノーパンダそのまま野外プレとかどうすか?
Wow, wow!
うわ、やば!
What are you thinking?
何考えてる?
You've never done it, right?
やったことないでしょ?
Let the maid be the maid.
メイドにメイドさせて
It's true.
ほんとだよね
What kind of cosplay?
どんなコスプレ?
I don't think I can stand it any longer,
ちょっともう多分我慢できないと思うからさ、
Other prepared people and fans.
他の用意した人たちと、ファン
Three fans?
ファンの3人?
Fans, fans.
ファン、ファン達
Fan, ABC.
ファン、ABC
ABC
ABC, can I call you?
ABC、呼んでいいかな?
ABC, it's okay.
ABC、大丈夫です
Can I call you?
呼んでいい?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
yes.
はい
Well then, if you just call me.
じゃあ、ちょっと呼んでくれば
yes.
はい
Yes, I'm here.
はい、来ました
But isn't it dangerous for me?
でも、やばくないですか、俺
By the way, who prepared this?
ちなみにこれ用意したの、誰?
ABC's, I don't understand.
ABCの、分かんない
Who is ABC?
ABCの誰?
Mr. A doesn't understand, either.
Aさんが、だってその子も分かんないでしょ、
someone.
誰か
surely.
確かに
Mr. A, Mr. B, and Mr. C.
Aさん、Bさん、Cさん
So, may I introduce myself again?
じゃあ、改めて自己紹介させてもらいます?
For now, please only ask those who have prepared it.
とりあえず、用意した人だけ頼み入れていただいて
The person who prepared it.
用 意した人はね
So, is it necessary?
じゃあ、必要?
that.
それ
Not necessary.
必 要ない
need?
必要?
It's not necessary.
必要ない
Want to know?
知りたい?
Ah, I see.
ああ、なるほどかな
ああ、なるほどね
It's like everyone is dying to attack.
もう、みんな襲いたくてしょうがないみたいな感じでさ
It's because everyone has that kind of aura.
なんか、そういうオーラがみんな出ちゃってるからさ
You understand, right?
分かるでしょ?
I feel like I'm about to be attacked.
今から襲われます、みたいな
It's like I'm about to be attacked.
今から襲われるんだ、みたいな
Please stand up for a moment.
ちょっとさ、一回立ってみてよ
Here?
ここね?
Isn't it erotic?
エロくない?
So, turn around a little bit.
じゃあ、ちょっと後ろ向いて
behind?
後 ろ?
That's naughty.
エッチですね
This is what makes me move backwards.
後ろにさせられてるの、これ
At the back.
後ろに
After all, 18-year-olds should be allowed to do all kinds of cosplay.
やっぱさ、18歳の子にはさ、やっぱりいろんなコスプレさせてあ
Ge Taijan.
げ たいじゃん
What the heck.
なんなんなん
You like cute clothes, right?
かわいい服とか、好きでしょ?
like.
好き
There's no point in having an old lady cosplay.
おばさんにコスプレさせてもしょうがないんだからさ
No, I'm here, but I'm not too aggressive.
いや、来たけど、これ攻めすぎない
a little bit.
ちょっと
Ah, I see.
ああ、なるほどね
So, please sit down for a moment.
じゃあ、ちょっと座ってもらって
So, is that enough?
じゃあ、もういい?
please.
どうぞ
Well then, I'll have it.
じゃあ、いただきます
Please have it.
いただいてください
Well then, round two.
じゃあ、2回戦
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
Please have it.
いただいてください
It suits you perfectly.
最高に似合ってます
What is this?
これは、これは一体何ですか?
This is an erotic costume.
これは、エロいコスです
What on earth is this?
これは、一体何ですか?
This is an erotic costume.
これは、エロいコスです
Sorry, this is probably the chosen costume.
すいません、たぶんに選ばれたコスです
White, white, white.
白、白、白
White, you like white, right?
白、白好きでしょ?
I like white.
白好き
Everyone can't stand it now.
今、みんな我慢できない
Maybe.
たぶんさ
what up?
どうした?
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
Then lick it happily.
じゃあ、うれしそうに舐めてね
Do I have to say it?
言 わなくてもいいか?
Oh-kun, can you do this?
おうくん、こうやられる?
O-kun, can you do this?
お うくん、こうやられる?
painful?
苦しい?
So, it's like this.
じゃあ、こんな感じ
It's like this.
こんな感じだよ
What?
何を?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいわ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
My spatula.
自分のヘラが
Ah, okay.
あ、 いいよ
So cute.
すごいかわいい
It was amazing just now, I guess.
さっきはすごいね、なんか
This person is in constant pain.
この人、ずっと苦にしてるね
It's been a long time, it's been a long time.
長いね、ずっとしてるね
It's delicious, I'm sorry, but I have to drink it.
美味しいんだね、すみません、飲まないと
I'm fine, I have a dick.
元気だね、なんかちんこがね
Looks like it'll work, this one.
いけそうだね、これちんこ
That person is fine.
その人ね、元気だね
It's ticking.
カチカチだね
yeah?
ん?
It's ticking.
カチカチだね
I have to tell you.
言ってもらわないと
Lick the water.
水気舐めさね
Lick it all the time, keep on licking it.
ずっと舐めさね、もくもくと
It looks like it was delicious.
美味しかったみたいだよ